

SHRIDIVYA



Dubai, UAE



+971528993623



Divya00p@gmail.com



SKILLS

- Networking
- Computer Security
- Computer Architecture
- PL/SQL, Linux & VMWare
- Windows server/Active directory
- Incident/Problem management
- **Scripting Skills: Strong** scripting (e.g. Python) and automation skills.
- **Operating Systems: Windows** and Linux system administration



TRAINING & CERTIFICATONS

- Administering and Deploying System Center 2012 Configuration Manager (70-243)
- ITIL foundation v3
- **AWS Trained**



CALLANGUAGES

English, Tamil, Arabic (basic) & Hindi (Basic)

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Received "Best Performer" Award for providing good service to clients from MOE
- Handled many trainings to clients to adopt new technologies

PERSONAL INFORMATION

: Shridivya.P Name Date of Birth: Dec 5, 1990 Marital Status: Married Visa Status : Husband visa

AWS / AZURE cloud Engineer & IT System Administrator



PROFILE • ABOUT ME

I have over 6+ years of experience in infrastructure solutions, cloud technologies, networking, data center operations, platform migration and enterprise directories. Currently am looking forward for a challenging role in the field of Cloud Engineer & System Administration.

CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

- **Excellent Problem-solving abilities**
- Highly skilled in providing technical maintenance and recovery maintenance to the local or wide area networks.
- Innovation skills and vision



WORK EXPERIENCE

Cloud Engineer

Ministry of Education deputed through ITQAN from Jul 2016-Mar 2019 Dubai

- Deploying, automating, maintaining and managing AWS cloud based production system, to ensure the availability, performance, scalability and security of productions systems.
- AWS experience with using a broad range of AWS technologies (e.g. EC2, RDS, ELB, S3, Glacier, RDS, IAM, Cloud Watch, Lambda, Auto scaling) to develop and maintain an Amazon AWS based cloud solution, with an emphasis on best practice cloud security.

System Administrator

Accenture Service Private Ltd from Jun 2014- oct 2015, India

- Working on VMware Update manager for updating / patching for all the ESXi hosts and VMs.
- Responsible for the management of Servers and proactive monitoring of servers, responding the alerts.

IT Operation Analyst

Qsource Pvt Ltd deputed through Accenture From Oct 2012-Jun2014. India

- Maintaining Accenture standard images (XP, Win7 and Win8) and providing L2 support for any issues related to images deployment or applications
- Coordinating with internal team like GLOBAL SERVICE DESK, GLOBAL INFORMATION SECURITY and Networking Team to provide effective customer support.



EDUCATION

- B. Tech (IT) in 2012 affiliated to Anjalai Ammal Mahalingam Engineering College (Anna University, Chennai) with8.17
- H.S.C with 84% from Schwartz matric Higher Secondary School, Ramnad, Tamilnadu in 2008.